

SEO MANAGER

Details

Bengaluru India 9529922708 swati.sharma753@gmail.com

Skills

SEO

Google Search Console

Google Analytics

HTML & CSS

Google Adwords

JavaScript

Hobbies

Poetry Quote Writing

Profile

A performance-driven SEO professional with 7+ years of experience working at both in-house and client-based companies. I have recently demonstrated my skill by increasing ranking organic keywords from 10 to 3000+ and improve the organic traffic to 7% in just three months for my client (Individually).

Employment History

SEO Manager, The White Teak Company By Asian Paints, Bengaluru

OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

- Incharge of End to End Strategy and Implimention with the team of 2.
- Ranked website for more than 3000 business driven keywords
- Increased the monthly organic traffic by 87.5%
- Maintaining the Local Business for All the Store Locations (15) in the 3 Pack Results to increase footfall to the stores in various cities.

SEO Analyst, Toprankers, Bengaluru

OCTOBER 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2021

- Ranked the website for almost 100 competitive keywords Increased organic traffic by 25% so far. Generating around 15000 leads every month.
- Build 3 YouTube Channels from scratch. Generating potential leads from those channels.

SEO Account Manager, Symberity (Formerly Known As DPFOC), Jaipur

JULY 2017 - OCTOBER 2019

- Ranked websites in a competitive niche(Furniture/Medical/Hotel) at top 5 for 20+ high volume keywords.
- Increased organic traffic by 20% and reduced bounce rate by 10%
- Acquired quality editorial backlinks which helped to boost the ranks of the keywords.

Project Highlights:

- · Ezliving Furnitures Ireland
- · Killarney Hotels Ireland

SEO Executive, DLB Infotech, Jaipur

JANUARY 2016 - JANUARY 2017

- Incharge of outreach to acquire 100-150 quality backlinks for the business to get the trending keywords ranked on the top 3 positions to peek at the event.
- Generated 7-10 Lac revenue/ per event

Project Highlights:

Wi-Fi Study

Education

BCA, Rajasthan University, Jaipur

MARCH 2009 - APRIL 2012

MCA, Jaipur National University, Jaipur

MARCH 2014 - MARCH 2016